(Penny:)Okay, for the final touch,
this is an eyelash-curler.
(Penny:)You just place it on your lashes
and squeeze it closed.
(Amy:)Oh. I don't know.
(Amy:)Looks like something
used by Tinker Bell's gynecologist.
(Penny:)Who I hope, for her sake,
is not Captain Hook, so...
Who you calling?
- I'm gonna video-chat Sheldon.
- Hmm.
(Amy:)If my new look leads to phone sex...
...I'm gonna have to ask you
to leave the room.
(Alex:)Dr. Cooper's office.
(Amy:)Oh. Hello. Who are you?
(Alex:)I'm Alex, Dr. Cooper's assistant.
(Alex:)- Can I help you?
- I'd like to speak to Sheldon.
(Alex:)I'm sorry,
he's asked me to hold all calls...
(Alex:)...unless you're Stephen Hawking,
his mother, or himself from the future.
- All right, well, tell him Amy called.
- Last name?
(Amy:)He knows my last name.
I'm his girlfriend.
(Amy:)We have a contract and everything.
I'll send you a PDF.